Hello everyone, this year in Japan, it is already as hot as midsummer as of June.
Currently, we are on a bus heading to JR Tachikawa Station.
Today we will be riding the JR Chuo Line's limited express Azusa train from Tachikawa, Tokyo to Matsumoto, Nagano.
Since Matsumoto can be reached in about 2 hours by express train, it is recommended that it is easy to reach from Tokyo.
We have arrived at Tachikawa Station.
First, we will buy a box lunch to eat on the train.
Today, I bought a chilled salmon with dashi chazuke (chilled soup stock), priced at 540 JPY / the 4 USD.
Now let's head for the platform.
A freight train is stopping. I personally think containers are very cool, but what do you think?
The Azusa limited express train is coming.
The black and white with purple accents is beautiful.
Since Tachikawa is not the first station, the transfer time is short, but we boarded the train without haste.
We are safely seated in my reserved seat,
I will be with you for two short hours from here.
We are departing with a view of the west Tokyo cityscape.
On the back of the table, there was a warning written.
Oops... I didn't expect to find an outlet....
There it is, on the underside of the seat. This is very helpful.
Free WiFi is also available.
The men's restroom was like this.
It's a little embarrassing that you can see my back.
I'm going inside.
There is a handle inside, so it is safe even if it shakes.
About 45 minutes after leaving Tachikawa, an open area appeared after passing through the mountains.
it was very pleasant to be free from the cramped, tunnel-filled scenery.
I was getting hungry by now, so I’l eat my lunch.
Neighbor is a sushi roll, which looks delicious.
I prepare it as soon as possible.
First, take out the ingredients.
Pour in the broth, being careful not to spill.
Put the ingredients into the broth one by one.
Finally, sprinkle furikake over the top and it is ready to serve.
Itadakimasu
Thank you for the meal, it was very delicious.
The farming area is spreading out.
we are getting much closer to our destination.
The scenery is very different from that of Tokyo, and it feels like we are in the countryside.
Approaching a residential area. Our destination is just around the corner.
We finally arrived at Matsumoto Station, the last stop of the tour.
Here is the platform of Matsumoto station.
Thank you for the 2-hour trip by Azusa.
Welcom to Matsumoto
I was short of cash, so I recharged and tried again.
The fare was 5650JPY / 42 USD.
The east exit of Matsumoto station.
After this, we headed to a hot spring hotel.
See you again, Bye!